Tomorrow at noon,
you will have a visitor.
But you must not meet him.
You must not go to the visitation room.
Someone's here to see you.
Turn around. Go back to your room!
Dad…
Johngalli A.
This man was behind it all.
Johngalli A. is,
without a doubt, a Stand user.
Just know that you are being targeted.
I'll get you out immediately.
My handcuffs!
When did I get free?
Jolyne, get away from that door!
Star Platinum: The World!
Time, stop!
What happened just now?
Stay still! The fight has already begun.
Aerodynamics.
It detected our positions
using aerodynamics.
Do not make a move
until we understand the contraption.
Don't order me around.
-I know that!
-You… FE40536!
Who do you think you're talking to?
You bastard!
Jolyne!
-You…
-Don't move!
Keep your voice down.
It'll detect our position again.
Johngalli A. uses
that Stand to read the airflow.
It may even react
to the change in our breathing.
Plus, that Stand can be used remotely.
He can shoot at that Stand
to reflect the bullet to his target.
It's a sniping Stand.
We cannot attack Johngalli A.,
who is in the men's prison.
We have to destroy that long-range Stand.
Any damage dealt
to the Stand is reflected on its user.
I'm well aware.
The problem is,
the moment we move to prompt an attack,
the Stand will detect our position
and Johngalli A. will shoot at us.
Stay by the wall, Jolyne!
It's detecting your location!
Jolyne,
what are you thinking?
EPISODE 4: THE VISITOR (2)
Your own muscles cannot be trusted.
When skin comes in contact with a breeze,
the muscles have a twitching reflex.
This is an automatic reflex
you cannot control.
Therefore, I use my bones
to affix the rifle.
Bones land firmly on the surface.
The gun is as stable
as the surface itself.
Its stability is something we can trust.
Meteorologists may argue
that the direction of drafts
cannot be predicted.
That may be true, but only to an extent.
Is this fly flying randomly?
No.
It flies while smelling things nearby
and feeling the air current.
The wind is the fly's movement.
Just as the guard said,
Jotaro Kujo is here.
He's here to see
his daughter, Jolyne Cujoh.
The descendant of the Joestars
is in the visitation room
at this very moment.
Within range of my ability,
Downtown Transfer.
Joestar…
Joestar!
My life will finally begin
after I eradicate your family's blood!
You will pay for robbing me
of the one who was my rock!
I see.
You said we have to destroy it, right?
Look at its movement.
It can't detect the wind
due to the precipitation.
Now's my chance! Stone Ocean!
No, wait! Look closer!
It's evading every drop of water.
It's reading the drops' air current
to avoid them.
Jolyne, go back to the wall!
He's going to shoot at us!
This isn't good.
Once the guards arrive, the air will stir!
-Hey, listen!
-What?
Hurry, move the base of the pillar!
Kick it with all your might!
-But you're…
-Don't worry about me.
Got that? Please don't forget what I said.
I want you to survive!
I don't know why,
but there's a descending hole
between the walls.
It seems to be a passage.
Maybe it leads to
the sewer or the vent.
What is this?
It may lead us to the outside.
Let's go, Jolyne.
Seems it's our only option.
-It flew away…
-No.
It's still close.
It's looking for
the perfect angle to snipe us.
No…
It's following the boy
on the other side of this door.
He plans to hunt the boy
because he helped us escape.
Jolyne, go down the hole!
I came to break you out!
Before I entered this room…
he grabbed this arm of mine.
I'm sure of it.
I can't believe it, but he's here.
He was just an ordinary kid
like you'd see at any park.
And we don't know each other…
We're complete strangers.
But…
he grabbed my arm
with desperation in his eyes.
The warmth of his hand
even felt as if he cared about me.
I'm going back inside.
Before he shoots the boy,
I'll kill Johngalli A.!
Good grief.
To the visitation room!
That's where the fire alarm went off!
There are no cameras there.
-Be prepared to engage!
-Where did he go?
That boy…
How does he move through this place,
appearing and disappearing
out of nowhere?
Hurry! To Visitation Room B!
Did that boy dig this hole?
This wall… So he used this!
His height is about 140cm.
His build is small, almost like a child's.
I don't know who he is,
but the hole
that suddenly opened is a vent.
I know where it leads by reading the air.
However…
I can't have this small guy
guide Jotaro and his daughter
deep underground
where I cannot reach them!
I will not lose those two again!
I'll finish this small one first!
Jolyne,
our situation is too dire.
Our Stands are only good
for defense at the moment.
Should we strike, Johngalli A. will read
the movement of the air.
This is too dangerous.
Hey, you!
You can't just leave the room!
This side is the prison!
-Good grief.
-Leave from the other side!
What the…
There it is!
Just as I thought, it's chasing the boy!
But there aren't any windows here.
How can he aim through the men's prison?
No… However…
This boy… Look at him!
How smart!
No, we're blessed!
With his body submerged completely
underwater, the air is unaffected!
And, he's inside a pipe!
Johngalli A. cannot find him now!
Not only that,
there are no windows down here.
Surely he can't shoot him now…
The pipe is bursting! But how?
Where is he aiming from?
Could he be…
Distance to the target is 321m.
The bullet drops 9,5cm while airborne,
and there's a slight ocean breeze of
3,2 meters per second.
The bullet will drift
by 4,2cm to the left.
Finding its target.
Targeting his heart.
Shit!
Stone Ocean!
Threads!
Jolyne Cujoh… This is her Stand ability!
She followed the boy down?
Is she an imbecile!
She thinks her net can stop my bullet?
Changing my target to Jolyne Cujoh.
Targeting the forehead.
Now, shoot!
How?
I'm so glad I broke this pipe beforehand.
The moment I came in,
I punctured this gas line.
Gas is lighter than air.
It creates a layer of gas
separate from oxygen.
I thought it would obscure your aim.
Man, was I right.
How did she do this?
You're too late! You're mine now!
Stone Ocean!
Seems you couldn't read your own fate.
STAND NAME: DOWNTOWN TRANSFER
STAND MASTER: JOHNGALLI A.
Who are you?
How is a child like you
roaming freely about this prison?
I hit myself.
This bone.
That's right. You gave me this.
What is it?
It looks like a bone. What's going on?
You tried to stop me
from going to the visitation room.
Just what do you know?
Hey, answer me!
Not yet… I can't, yet.
You mustn't let that go.
This smell.
Is this your doing?
That sniper guy, Johngalli A., his Stand?
It was nothing once I got to it.
I pounded it into a thousand pieces.
I see.
It seems you're quite used to
fighting with your Stand.
Not out of choice…
There he is! Right there!
He's on the move!
Hide! He has a rifle.
He's hiding behind that pipe.
I saw him going above the tank!
That's impossible.
He was targeting from the men's prison,
which is 200 to 300m away.
There are layers of bars between us.
Not only that,
he is almost completely blind.
How do you suppose he traveled so fast?
How the hell should I know?
If I said he's here, he's here!
Hide!
He's directly above you!
All right, I believe you.
And get ready.
The gas must have been accumulating.
We did it!
Hey, we're safe now!
What the…
Where did he run off to?
Are you hiding?
You don't have to be afraid anymore.
Come out and explain what's going on!
What are you doing?
I'm looking for the boy.
Did you see where he went?
I don't understand what you mean.
What boy are you talking about?
Oh, I see.
You didn't see him, did you?
I was talking to a little boy
outside the visitation room.
Johngalli A. tried to
get rid of him first.
Get rid of him?
What are you talking about?
You came here on your own.
And so I followed you.
Hold on, our stories aren't matching up.
You must have heard his voice.
No, I know you did!
He's the one who told us
about the secret passage!
You were there with me!
Did you hear a ghost or something?
I don't know of a secret passage.
Damn you! You're messing with me
at a time like this?
You're here now because
you followed me down the secret tunnel…
Hold on…
Something's not right with you.
Your wound…
You were shot.
What happened to your wound?
Wound?
The bullet wound
from when Johngalli A. shot you!
On your right shoulder.
But you aren't bleeding, and your clothes…
I don't have a scratch
from being shot either!
This man…
He isn't Johngalli A.!
He's the prison guard!
But I saw him get shot through the head!
His head is unscathed!
What do you mean he was shot?
And who is Johngalli A.?
What's going on?
Something's amiss.
It's not adding up!
What is this?
A fate more terrible than death
will await us all.
You must not go to the visitation room.
The visitation room…
That's right. Something was off
from the very beginning.
When was I uncuffed?
And that bullet…
Was I really shot back there?
But my dad and I don't have a scratch.
Was Johngalli A.
attacking us to begin with?
Something's wrong.
Nothing is making sense!
This isn't reality!
I'm in a dream of some sort.
No, I'm under someone's spell!
This is…
A dream…
Was I… dreaming?
Since when…
It looks like I did
knock out this prison guard.
This photo of Johngalli A…
Dad showed it to me.
The accident with the hitchhiker.
I heard that it was all
a plot to imprison me.
That was all real.
And then I tried to leave the room.
That's when I noticed I was uncuffed.
That was the moment.
No, I was sitting down when I awoke.
So before then…
We haven't stepped outside
of this visitation room.
In other words…
Johngalli A.'s Stand
was an illusion my mind created.
The secret passageway too.
The moment we stepped into
this visitation room,
we fell under their trap
and were forced to dream.
As if engulfed by a python,
slowly but surely,
we're being melted to the bone!
The boy in the garbage can
who gave me this bone.
He was real!
I was able to wake up
because I cut myself on this bone!
Without the pain from the cut,
I would have stayed asleep.
This ability is Johngalli A.'s attack!
My thread! I can't unravel it,
not even for a few centimeters!
This is bad!
Dammit.
I'm getting sleepy again…
We need to get out of here.
Out of this visitation room!
Stone Ocean!
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter